☆独家制作☆
喜马拉雅主播 & 微信公众号:
美国青少年英语
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
[distorted cheering]
[yelling and cheering]
["r.o.c.k. In the u.s.a." playing]
♪ rockin' in the u.s.a. ♪
[squealing and laughing]
♪ hey! R.o.c.k. In the u.s.a... ♪
- [man] one for each of you.
- Thanks.
‎一人一个
[vendor] have fun.
‎-谢谢
‎-玩得开心
♪ r.o.c.k. In the u.s.a. ♪
♪ yeah, yeah ♪
♪ rockin' in the u.s.a. ♪
- [man 2] there you go.
- Yeah!
‎-给你
‎-太好了！
["the washington post march" playing]
[crowd cheering]
- [band stops]
- now, doesn't that just lift your spirits?
‎这乐曲是不是特别振奋人心？
[cheering]
let's give another big hand for
the hawkins high marching band!
‎让我们再次
‎用掌声鼓励霍金斯高中军乐队！
[cheering]
I hope you're all having
a good time tonight.
‎希望你们今晚都玩得开心
- [Crowd cheers]
- are you having a good time?
‎大家玩得开心吗？
[cheering]
[larry] I can't hear you!
‎我听不到
Are you having a good time?
‎你们玩得开心吗？
[loud cheering]
[chuckles] I want you to
know that we spared no expense
‎我想告诉大家
‎我们可是不惜一切代价
to provide you with the very best
entertainment that money can buy!
‎给大家提供能买得到的最好的娱乐
[fair worker] keep your arms inside.
‎手臂不要伸出去
Uh-oh! Dad can't get out now.
‎爸爸这下子出不去了
Why do you two enjoy torturing me?
‎你们为什么这么喜欢折磨我？
- Because it's fun.
- Yeah, dad, 'cause it's fun!
‎-因为好玩啊
‎-是的 爸爸 因为好玩
- Oh, here we go.
- [Ted groans]
‎开始了
[ted] oh, boy.
‎老天
hoo!
But enough of me blabbering.
‎我也不想再多啰嗦了
Who here wants to see some fireworks?
‎有谁想看烟花？
[cheering]
come on, now, you can
do better than that.
‎拜托 你们可以更投入一点的
Who here wants to see some fireworks?
‎有谁想看烟花？
[loud cheering]
["semper fidelis" playing]
[karen sighs]
uh, why are we stopping?
‎我们为什么停下来了？
Because I slipped jimmy a five.
‎因为我偷偷给吉米塞了五块钱
You what?
‎你做了什么？
Come on, these are the
best seats in the house.
‎拜托 这可是全场最佳的观赏座位
The best seats in the house.
‎全场最佳观赏座位
- [Fireworks popping]
- oh!
Happy fourth of july!
‎独立日快乐！
[cheering]
[karen] whoa!
[laughing]
- that was pretty, wasn't it?
- Yeah.
‎-真漂亮 对吧？
‎-是的
Yeah.
‎是的
[karen gasps]
[ominous synth music playing]
[rustling in trees]
mom, the trees.
‎妈妈 树
- What, baby?
- The trees are moving.
‎-怎么了 宝贝？
‎-树在动
[rustling continues]
why are you looking at the trees, baby?
‎你为什么要看树啊 宝贝？
The fireworks. Look at the fireworks!
‎有烟花 看烟花呀
[karen laughs] that was
a big one, wasn't it?
‎刚刚那个真大 是不是？
[thudding footsteps]
[creature snarling]
‎NETFLIX 原创剧集
[theme song playing]
‎第七集：咬伤
[fireworks popping and
crackling distantly]
[crowd cheering distantly]
[marching band playing distantly]
[eleven] he said he
was building something.
‎他说他在搭建一个什么东西
That it was all for me.
‎而且都是为我搭建的
Building something...
‎搭建某些东西...
- Is he talking about the flayed?
- He must be.
‎-他想说的是被夺心者吗？
‎-肯定是
So, he's building an
army, just like we thought.
‎所以正如我们所想的
‎他在组建一支军队
Yeah, but he's not building
this army to spread.
‎是的 但他组建这支军队
‎并不是为了散播出去
He's building it to stop eleven.
‎而是为了阻止十一
Last year, el closed the gate on him.
‎去年 艾尔当着他的面关上了门
I have a feeling that
really pissed him off.
‎我感觉他真的被气坏了
Like, royally.
‎气疯了
And the mind flayer now knows that
‎夺心魔现在知道了
‎她是唯一可以阻止他的人
she's the only thing that can stop him.
- But if she's out of the way...
- Game over.
‎-但如果她无法参与了...
‎-游戏就结束了
He also said
‎他还说他会杀了你们所有人
he was gonna kill all of you.
Yeah, well, that's nice.
‎好吧 挺好的
[faint screeching noise]
[ominous synth music playing]
do you guys hear that?
‎你们听到了吗？
[nancy shudders]
it's just the fireworks.
‎只是烟花而已
Billy...
‎比利
When he told you this,
it was here, in this room?
‎他告诉你这些的时候
‎是在这里吗？就在这个房间里？
[distant thudding noise]
[fluttering sound]
he knows we're here.
‎他知道我们在这里了
[trees rustling]
[creature snarls]
[creature screeches]
[alarm blaring]
[slurring] jesus, slow down!
‎老天 慢一点！
[slurring] yeah, what is
this, like, the indy 500?
‎老天 这是什么？印地500赛车吗？
It's the indy 300.
‎是印地300赛车
- No, dingus, it's 500!
- It's 300!
‎-不 蠢瓜 是印地500
‎-是印地300
Let's say a million.
‎那就一百万吧
[both laughing loudly]
- what is wrong with them?
- I don't know.
‎-他们怎么了？
‎-我不知道
- [Erica] dustin, watch out!
- [Dustin] shit!
‎-达斯汀 小心！
‎-妈的！
[steve grunts, yells]
- oh!
- [Robin groans]
you guys all right back there?
‎你们没事吧？
[both groaning]
they're fine.
‎他们没事
Come on. We gotta go, now.
‎快点 我们得走了 就现在
- Come on! Get out!
- Let's go!
‎-快出来啊！
‎-我们走了！
[steve] ow!
- [Steve] we're coming!
- Here goes nothin'.
‎-我们来了
‎-不管那么多了
- [Steve] this sucks.
- [Beeping]
‎真没劲
[robin and steve whooping giddily]
- hey! You look like you're surfing!
- Surfing! Yeah!
‎-你看起来像在冲浪
‎-是的！
[steve] whoa!
- They seem drunk.
- Why would they be drunk?
‎-他们看起来像是喝醉了
‎-他们怎么会喝醉？
I'm a natural! Check it out!
‎我可有天赋了 看好了
Whoop!
[robin laughs]
wipeout!
‎被浪打翻了！
[both laughing]
- he's burning up.
- [Steve] you're burning up.
‎-他发高烧了
‎-你才发高烧了
- One sec, one sec. Steve, steve.
- [Steve] god, no.
‎-等一下 史蒂夫
‎-老天 不要
ow!
His pupils are super dilated.
‎他的瞳孔扩张地很严重
Maybe he's drugged.
‎也许他被下了药
Ugh. Boop!
Steve, are you drugged?
‎史蒂夫 你被下药了吗？
How many times, dad?
‎需要我说多少次啊 爸爸？
‎我不吸毒的 只抽大麻
I don't do drugs. It's only marijuana.
This isn't funny, okay? I need
to know what they did to you.
‎这不好笑 好吗？
‎我需要知道他们对你做了什么
- Are you gonna die on us?
- Boop.
‎你会死吗？
We all die, my strange
little child friend.
‎我们都会死的 我奇怪的小小朋友
It's just a matter of how...
‎重点只是方式和时间
And when.
They're gonna be
looking for us up there,
‎上了地面他们会追捕我们
so I need you to tell me
where you parked your car.
‎我需要你告诉我你把车停在哪里了
Oh, can we make a pit
stop at the food court?
‎我们能去餐饮区停一停吗？
- I would kill for a hot dog on a stick.
- Ooh!
‎-我死都想来一个热狗串
‎-好吧
All right. Yeah, food.
‎没错 食物 是的 你们想吃多少都行
Yes, you can have as
much food as you want,
but only if you tell me
where your car is parked.
‎前提是要告诉我你们的车停在哪里
- Uh-oh.
- Uh-oh?
‎-啊哦
‎-啊哦？
The car's off the board.
‎车开不了了
- What?
- They took the keys.
‎-什么？
‎-他们把钥匙给拿走了
The russians, they took the keys.
‎俄国人把钥匙给拿走了
Like, forever ago.
‎很久很久之前就拿走了
[robin and steve laugh]
that's a bummer, right?
‎令人失望了 是吧？
[robin laughing]
[robin and steve] oh!
Oh, my god, that tastes so good. Ah!
‎天哪 味道太好了
Steve, can you taste the air?
‎史蒂夫 你能尝到空气的味道吗？
I taste it! I taste it!
‎我尝到了！
- Stop!
- Shit! Come on! Come on!
‎-停下！
‎-妈的！快走！
- [Kids clamoring]
- [in russian] stop right there!
‎快来！
- [Robin] okay, okay, okay! Woo!
- Why are we running?
‎-好的！
‎-我们为什么要跑？
[robin laughing]
[eleven grunting]
[mike] yeah. That's good like that.
‎是的 这样就很好
Hey, get away from the windows.
‎嘿 离窗口远一点
[all panting]
[lamp squeaking]
[rumbling]
[electric crackling]
[gasping]
[breathing rapidly]
it's close.
‎它接近了
[leaves rustling]
[branches snapping]
[rumbling footsteps]
[glasses clinking]
[rumbling stops]
where'd it go?
‎它去哪儿了？
[nancy exhales sharply]
[shuddering breaths]
- [creature shrieks]
- [all gasping]
[yells, grunts]
- [creature shrieks]
- [jonathan grunts]
[jonathan yells]
[grunts]
- [shrieks]
- [jonathan groans]
[shrieks]
[creature wails, screeches]
[creature wails]
[shrieking in pain]
[gasps]
[creature shrieking]
[creature screams]
[eleven yells]
[creature shrieks]
[max yelps]
holy shit.
‎妈呀
[shrieking]
- [glass shatters]
- [shrieking]
[panting]
[creatures shrieking]
[shrieking and barking]
[yells]
- [whimpering shrieks]
- [panting]
[roaring and shrieking]
[eleven screams]
el!
‎艾尔！
[screaming]
[mike] el!
‎艾尔！
- [All grunting]
- [creature roaring]
[pumps shotgun]
[roaring]
[mike] pull!
‎救命！
[jonathan] nancy, shoot it!
‎南茜 快开枪！
[screaming]
[snarling]
[pained snarls]
[eleven screams]
[max] come on! Lucas!
‎快点 卢卡斯！
[nancy pumps shotgun]
[yells]
[roars]
[lucas grunts, yells]
[shotgun fires]
[roaring]
[screaming]
- [kids straining]
- [creature roars]
[yells]
[max] pull!
- [Shotgun fires]
- [creature screeches]
- [squelching]
- [roaring]
el! El, you okay?
‎艾尔 你没事吧？
[creature roaring]
[shrieking]
[screeching in pain]
[monstrous chittering]
[creature snarls]
[panting heavily]
[roaring]
[eleven panting]
[creature shrieking]
[roaring]
[yelling]
[pained screeching]
[yells]
[distant roaring]
- [nancy] go, go, go!
- [Jonathan] come on, come on, go!
‎-走！我们走！
‎-快走！
- [Nancy] go!
- [Jonathan] hurry up! Come on!
‎-走！
‎-抓紧时间 快走！
[mike] everybody out!
‎所有人都出去！
- [Jonathan] go!
- [Nancy] go, come on!
‎-快走！
- [Creature roars]
- [jonathan] go, go, go, go!
‎快走！
- [Lucas] come on!
- [Nancy repeating] come on!
‎赶紧的！
[lucas] come on! Come on!
‎快点
[creature shrieking]
[jonathan] get in. Right here.
[eleven wails in pain]
- drive! Drive!
- [Engine starting]
‎快开车！
[roaring]
- [steve] whoa!
- Where are we going?
‎-我们要去哪儿？
‎-相信我就行
- Just trust me.
- [Robin laughs]
all clear.
‎安全
[score from back to the future playing]
[marty] doc!
What did I tell you?!
‎我怎么和你说的来着？
Eighty-eight miles per hour!
‎时速141公里！
[dustin] come on.
‎快来
- [Metal clanging in movie]
- [doc gasps]
[doc] the temporal displacement
occurred exactly 1:20...
‎时间位移已经发生！
‎-恰好在凌晨1点20分
‎-你们俩坐下
- You two, sit.
- No, no, no! These seats are too close!
‎不行 这里的位置太靠前了
- Dude, these seats blow.
- Then don't watch the movie.
‎-朋友 这个座位太差劲了
‎-那就别看电影
- We wanna watch it.
- Then watch it!
‎-我们想看
‎-那就看！
- Shh!
Sorry.
‎对不起
Whatever you do,
‎不管你们做什么 不要离开这里
don't... Go... Anywhere.
- Fine, dad.
- [Robin snickers]
‎-行吧 爸爸
‎-那他们究竟在哪儿？
[doc] the appropriate question
is "when the hell are they?"
‎正确的问法是
‎"他们究竟在哪个时间？"
you see, einstein has just become
‎你瞧 爱因斯坦刚刚成为了
‎全世界第一位时空旅行者
- the world's first time traveler!
- Sorry. Sorry.
‎抱歉
- [Doc] I sent him... Into the future!
- [Dustin sighs]
‎我把他送入了未来
okay, it's official.
‎好吧 正式宣布
‎我绝对不会要孩子
I'm never having kids.
- What are we doing here?
- We're laying low.
‎-我们在这里干什么？
‎-避风头
Cooling off.
‎等事态冷静下来 就像奥斯瓦尔德
Like oswald.
Oswald was found in a
theater and shot to death.
‎奥斯瓦尔德在电影院被发现
‎被射杀身亡了
A week later.
‎那是一周后的事了
The point is, his plan didn't work.
‎重点是他的计划没有成功
Only because it was a setup.
‎那是因为这一切都是陷阱
- What?
- He was just a patsy.
‎-什么？
‎-他只是个糊涂蛋
- Tell me you're joking.
- Shh!
‎告诉我你在开玩笑
[erica and dustin] shh!
We need to get outta here.
‎我们得离开这里
All right, you watch
tweedledee and tweedledum.
‎好吧 你在这儿看着丁当兄弟
- Make sure they don't go anywhere.
- Where are you going?
‎-确保他们不会离开
‎-你去哪儿？
To find us a ride.
‎去找交通工具
[doc] look out!
‎留神
[delorean zapping]
[brakes screeching]
[marty] doc...
- What's happening?
- I have no idea.
‎-什么情况？
‎-一无所知
[marty] are you telling me
that you built a time machine...
‎你是想告诉我你建了一个时空机吗？
[alexei speaking russian]
- what's he saying?
- He's showing me the location of the key
‎-他说什么？
‎-他在给我看关闭机器的
to turn off the machine.
‎那把钥匙的所在位置
[speaking russian]
- sorry, "keys". Two keys.
- [Alexei speaking russian]
‎抱歉 有两把钥匙
two-man rule.
‎二人管理制度
- Two-man rule?
- Yeah, two men, two keys, like a...
‎-二人管理制度？
‎-是的 两个人 两把钥匙 就像...
Nuclear launch.
‎核弹发射一样
But, uh, to retrieve the
keys, there is a vault.
‎但是为了拿到这两把钥匙
‎有一个地下室
- [Speaking russian]
- and to open the vault,
‎为了进入这个地下室
‎你需要输入普朗克常数
you need to enter planck's constant.
- Planck's what?
- Planck's constant.
‎-普朗克什么？
‎-普朗克常数
- It's a very famous number.
- All right, so we get the keys,
‎-是一个很出名的数字
‎-好吧 然后我们拿到钥匙
and then we turn the machine off.
‎然后把机器给关掉
That's what he says.
‎他就是这么说的
All right, well, that shouldn't
be too hard. We can do this.
‎听起来不难 我们能做到的
Joyce, did you hear the part
where he said the place was like
‎你没听到他说那个地方像是一个
an impenetrable fortress?
‎无法攻破的堡垒吗？
Yeah, but there has to be a way in.
‎是啊 但肯定有办法进去的
Yeah, there is. Our military.
‎的确有办法 我们的军队
- Who are coming.
- Well, we don't know that anymore
‎-军队在来的路上
‎-我们现在不能确定了
because you yelled at them like
it was a parent-teacher conference,
‎因为你像是在开家长会那样
‎冲着他们大吼
and then you hung up on them, so
‎然后你还挂了电话
we don't know what the hell's going on,
‎所以我们不知道
‎现在的情况究竟怎么样
because now we're... Wait,
wait, what are we do... Oh!
‎因为我们在...慢着 我们在...
Wait, that's right!
‎慢着 对了
We're on our way to rescue our children
‎我们在去救我们孩子们的路上
from the big, bad fourth
of july celebration!
‎因为他们在参加那个
‎糟糕的大型独立日庆祝活动
You know what, if you can't
handle this, then just turn around
‎你知道吗 如果你受不了 那就掉头
and drop me off first.
‎但是先让我下车
What are you gonna do?
‎你要怎么办？
You gonna walk back to hawkins?
‎你要一路走回霍金斯？
I will do anything if
it gets me away from you!
‎为了摆脱你 我什么都愿意做
Children! Children! Children!
‎孩子们！
This interminable bickering
was amusing at first,
‎你们俩无休无止的拌嘴
‎一开始还挺有意思的
but it's getting very stale
‎但现在毫无新鲜感了
‎我们还要开很长时间
and we've still got a
long drive ahead of us.
So, why don't you two cut the horseshit
‎所以 你们俩能不能别瞎扯了
and get to the part where you admit
‎赶紧承认对彼此有暧昧的想法吧？
your sexual feelings for one another?
- Whoa!
- You are way off base, buddy!
‎你错得也太离谱了 朋友
Oh, spare me, spare me, spare me!
‎饶了我吧
Yes, yes, he's a brute. I know.
‎是的 他是挺野蛮的 我知道
Probably reminds you
of a bad relationship,
‎八成让你想起了一段不好的感情经历
and, gosh, you'd really like
a nice man to settle down with,
‎老天 你真的很想要一个善良的人
‎与他安稳下来
but, admit it,
‎但承认吧
‎你真的很好奇他的蛋蛋长什么样
you're real curious to know
what he's like in the sack.
And you. Ha!
‎还有你
Well, you're just a big manbaby
‎你就是个内心长不大的男孩
‎宁愿表现出强势的样子
who'd rather act tough
than show his true feelings,
‎也不愿意展现真感情
because the last time you
opened your heart, you got hurt.
‎因为你上一次敞开心扉的时候受了伤
‎哎呦真疼
Owie.
And now, rather than
admit these feelings,
‎而现在 你们不想承认彼此的感情
‎转而采用这种
you're dancing around one another
with this mind-numbing and
frankly boorish mating ritual.
‎让人头皮发麻的
‎老实说也很土的求偶方式
So, please, for my sake,
‎所以 拜托了 为了我着想
either quit your
bickering, or pull over,
‎要么闭上嘴别吵了
‎要么就停车 把衣服给扯掉
tear off those clothes,
and get it over with already!
‎赶紧做吧！
[gasps]
[deep sigh]
[in russian] what was that?
‎你刚刚说了什么？
[in russian] I told them
they should have sex.
‎我告诉他们说他俩应该做爱
They have not had sex?
‎他们还没做过爱？
no.
‎没有
[snickers]
[chuckles]
[both laughing]
[joyce mutters]
[alexei speaking russian]
[both laughing]
[murray laughs] oh! Oh!
[murray and alexei continue laughing]
‎（欢迎来到印第安纳州
‎请小心驾驶 谢谢）
[tires squealing]
[glass shattering]
[eleven groans]
okay, get her down.
‎好了 让她坐下
[nancy] okay.
‎好了
Lemme see.
‎让我看看
- Oh, shit.
- [Groans]
‎哦 该死
what... What... Hey, what are you doing?
‎什么...嘿 你做什么？
I'm cleaning the wound.
‎清洁伤口
No, first, we need to stop the bleeding,
‎不 首先我们需要先止血
then clean, then
disinfect, then bandage.
‎然后清洁 然后消毒 最后上绷带
I skateboard. Trust me.
‎我玩滑板的 相信我
Mike, hold this.
‎迈克 按住
[groans]
keep the pressure on
it, nice and firm, okay?
‎用力按住 维持住压力 好吗？
We're gonna need water, soap.
‎我们还需要水和肥皂
- Yeah, okay.
- All right.
‎-对 好的
‎-好
Does any of this help?
‎这里面有任何有用的吗？
no.
‎没有 去给我找一个毛巾和一个碗
Go get me a washcloth and a bowl.
- A bowl?
- Lucas.
‎-碗？
‎-卢卡斯
- Go.
- [Stammers] okay.
‎-走了
‎-好的
[groans]
[nancy] what did that
thing look like to you?
‎-你觉得那个东西看起来像什么？
‎-像医院里的那个东西
Like that thing in the
hospital, only bigger.
Yeah, a lot bigger.
‎-但是更大
‎-是 大很多
Like, tom and bruce, they
merged to become one, right?
‎汤姆和布鲁斯合为一体了 对不对？
And... And driscoll kept saying
‎德里斯科尔不停说
‎她需要回到源头那里去...
how she needed to go
back to the source...
Wait, you think driscoll's in there?
‎慢着 你觉得德里斯科尔也在里面？
Maybe.
‎也许吧
And... And... And maybe heather
‎海瑟和珍妮特可能也在里面
‎天知道还会有谁
and janet, too, and god knows who else.
I don't know how we're gonna
kill this thing, but if we do...
‎我不知道我们要怎么杀掉这个东西
- We kill all the flayed.
- And... We end this.
‎-但如果成功...
‎-就杀掉了所有被夺心者
‎然后 就能彻底搞定这件事
Maybe.
‎也许
All I know is...
‎我只知道一点 我们需要艾尔
We need el.
[lucas] bowl...
‎碗
Bowl...
- Why wouldn't it be with the cereal?
- I don't know.
‎-为什么不和麦片在一起？
‎-我不知道
What else do you use a bowl for?
‎要不然还能用碗干什么？
I... I don't know.
‎我不知道
[lucas sighs]
oh, shit.
‎哦 该死
‎（烟花）
Satan's baby.
‎撒旦的宝宝
You ever shot one of these suckers?
‎你点过这种吗？
No. Is it sweet?
‎没有 是不是挺酷的？
- That's an understatement.
- [Max] that doesn't look like a bowl.
‎-这么说太轻描淡写了
‎-那个看起来可不像碗
Nah, it's way better.
‎不 比碗强多了
There is a reason this warning
label says "18 or older".
‎这个上面写着"18岁以下不得使用"
‎是有原因的
This sucker is filled with
150 grains of black powder.
‎这家伙里面有150颗黑火药
Aka gunpowder.
‎也就是火药
Strap two of these together,
and it's bigger than an m-80.
‎把两个捆在一起 就比M80还要强劲
Five of them,
‎五个加在一起
we've got ourselves a stick of dynamite.
‎就成了一根炸药
You wanna kill that
thing with fireworks?
‎你想用炸药杀死那个东西？
Do you have a better idea?
‎你有更好的主意吗？
Uh, yeah. Eleven.
‎有啊 十一
Against that thing? She's
gonna need some backup.
‎对付那个东西？她需要后援
- Oh, my god.
- [Lucas scoffs]
‎老天
hold this.
‎拿着
[mike groans]
does that hurt?
‎这样痛吗？
Uh, not bad.
‎不算太糟糕
You're gonna have an awesome scar.
‎会留下一个很不错的伤疤的
You'll look even more badass.
‎你看起来会更加了不起
Bitchin'.
‎牛掰
Yeah, bitchin'.
‎没错 牛掰
[chuckles]
el...
‎艾尔
Yeah?
‎怎么了？
I've been meaning to tell you something.
‎有件事我也一直想告诉你
It's just, being broken up,
‎分手这件事
it's been hard.
‎挺难的
[distorted radio chatter]
and...
‎我现在喜欢
‎你和麦克斯是朋友这一点了
I like that you and max are friends now.
It's just, I was jealous
at first, and... And angry.
‎我一开始只是嫉妒了 生气
And that's why I said
all that stupid stuff.
‎所以才说了那些蠢话
And it's like I wanted
you all to myself.
‎就像我想一个人独占你
And now I realize how unfair that is.
‎现在我意识到这样太不公平了
And selfish. And, like... I'm sorry.
‎太自私了 我...我很抱歉
I just, like, I've never felt like this,
‎只是 我从未对任何人
‎有过这样的感觉...
you know, with anyone before...
And...
‎而且...
[sighs] you know, they
do say it makes you crazy.
‎他们也的确说那让人疯狂
What makes you crazy?
‎什么让人疯狂？
You never... You never
heard that term...
‎你没听说过这种说法...
You know, like the phrase, like...
‎就是有个说法 就是...
"blank makes you crazy",
like the word...
‎某东西让人发疯 就那个词...
- "Girlfriends"?
- No, no, no, no, not... Not girlfriends.
‎-女朋友？
‎-不是 不是女朋友
- "Boyfriends".
- No! No, no, not boyfriends either.
‎-男朋友
‎-不 也不是男朋友
- It's like... It's like a feeling or...
- [Softly] a feeling...
‎-像是某种感觉 或者...
‎-某种感觉...
Yeah, like something...
‎就像是...
‎比如老人就经常会对彼此说这个
Like, old people say it
to each other sometimes.
- Old people?
- Yeah.
‎-老人？
‎-是的
What I wanna say is...
‎我想说的是...
That I just...
‎我只是...
I know that I...
‎我知道我...
- [Dustin speaking via radio, garbled]
- [static popping]
[dustin, distorted via radio]
I repeat... This is a code red!
‎我重复 红色警报
- [Score from back to the future plays]
- dustin?
Mike?
‎-达斯汀？
‎-迈克？
- [Mike] dustin!
- Mike!
‎-达斯汀！
‎-迈克！
Oh, my god, you have to
listen. I know I've been mia,
‎老天 你必须要听我解释
‎我知道我失踪了
and I'm sorry, it's not because I'm mad.
‎很抱歉 不是因为我生气了
‎不过我的确是生气了
I mean, I actually was mad,
but it's also because I
was trapped underground
‎也是因为我被困在了地下
in a secret russian base.
‎在一个秘密俄国基地里
[garbled radio audio]
dustin, you're going way too
fast. I can't understand you.
‎达斯汀 你语速太快了 我听不明白
I know that sounds insane,
‎我知道这听起来很疯狂
‎但俄国人渗入了霍金斯
but the russians have
infiltrated hawkins!
The goddamn russians!
‎该死的俄国人！
And now... They're
using... To open the gate.
‎而现在 他们在用...开门
Dustin, you're... You're breaking up.
‎达斯汀 说话断断续续的
And now they're after us and
we don't have a way out of here,
‎现在他们在追捕我们
‎我们必须要想办法逃走
so I need you to come and
get us. Can nancy drive?
‎所以需要你们过来接我们
‎南茜能开车吗？
[garbled radio audio]
‎我们会在...
dustin, you're cutting out.
‎达斯汀 听不到了
- Mike?
- Dustin, you there?
‎-迈克？
‎-达斯汀 在吗？
Mike? Mike, do you copy?
‎迈克 听到了吗？
Dustin...
‎达斯汀...
[powering down noise]
shit! Not now. Please, not now. Mike!
‎该死 别在这个时候啊
‎拜托 别在这个时候 迈克！
- Dustin!
- Mike!
‎-达斯汀！
‎-迈克！
[static hissing]
what is it?
‎怎么了？
Do you have any batteries? Double-a?
‎你有电池吗？五号的
Why would I have batteries?
‎我怎么会有电池？
I always carry batteries.
‎我到哪儿都会带着电池
Then what's the problem?
‎那有什么问题？
I need eight.
‎-我需要八节电池
‎-八节？
Eight?
Shit. Guess we'll have to go to plan b.
‎该死 看来我们得用B计划了
Plan b? What's plan b?
‎B计划？B计划是什么？
[film score crescendos]
where... Are they?
‎他们在哪儿？
That's amazing.
‎真棒
So, like, I wasn't totally focused
in there or anything, but...
‎我刚在里面
‎并没有完全集中注意力什么的
I'm pretty sure...
‎但我基本上可以肯定
That mom was trying to bang her son.
‎那个妈妈想要和她儿子做爱
Wait, wait, the hot chick
was alex p. Keaton's mom?
‎慢着 亚历克斯P基顿的妈妈？
Yeah, I'm pretty sure.
‎是啊 我挺确信的
But they're the same age.
‎但他们俩一样大啊
No, but he went back in time.
‎但他是时空穿梭回去的
[snickers]
then why is it called
back to the future?
‎那为什么片名要叫做《回到未来》？
He has to go back to the future
‎他必须要回到未来
because he's in the past.
‎因为他在过去
So, the future is actually the present,
‎所以未来实际上就是现在
‎也就是他自己的时间
which is his time.
Wh... What?
No, no, it's my turn. You've had enough.
‎-什么？
‎-不 轮到我了 你喝够了
[robin grunts contentedly]
[gentle synth music playing]
[echoing] wow.
[twinkling]
[echoing] hey, robin.
‎嘿 罗宾
You gotta check this out.
‎你得来看看这个
- [Grunts]
- check this...
‎你瞧...这个天花板 真漂亮
This... The ceiling, it's beautiful.
[echoing] oh, wow.
[chuckles]
oh.
[robin chuckles]
[grunts]
[steve groans]
[synth music distorts]
[twinkling]
[steve grunts]
[robin coughs]
[robin retches and spits]
[cheering]
[carnival music playing]
[hopper yells]
stay here, go over the
plans with smirnoff.
‎你待在这里
‎和斯米诺伏特加过一遍我们的计划
- I can help look.
- No, you'll scare the children.
‎-我能帮你们一起找
‎-不 你会吓到孩子们的
- Jim, if this is about earlier...
- Stay put, freud!
‎-吉姆 如果是因为之前的事...
‎-待着别动 弗洛伊德！
You hear me? Stay put!
‎听见了没？待着别动
[murray sighs]
[kids screaming and laughing]
you know, say what you will about kline,
‎你可以随意批评克莱恩
he certainly knows how to throw a party.
‎但他确实知道派对要怎么搞
I'm sorry about him, by the way.
‎顺便说 他的事情我很抱歉
- Who, larry?
- No, murray.
‎-谁 拉里？
‎-不 穆雷
He's a sick individual who
likes to get under people's skin.
‎他是个有病的家伙 喜欢激怒别人
So, let's not let him, you
know, get under our skin.
‎所以 我们可别被他激怒了
I'm not, I haven't.
‎-不会的 我没有
‎-你只是突然比平时安静了
I just, you seem a little
more quiet than usual.
- I just... I just wanna find the kids.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
‎-我只想找到孩子们
‎-是
[larry] I'll give it my best shot.
‎我会尽力而为
- [Bell clanging]
- [larry exclaims]
[man] you won yourself a bear!
Thank you. Here you go. [chuckles]
‎谢谢 给你
[photographer] mayor kline!
‎克莱恩市长！
[photographer] one more, one more.
‎再来一张
[photographer] big smile. There we go.
‎笑一个 好嘞
[cheering]
- watch it!
- [Man 2] happy fourth, dick.
‎-小心点！
‎-独立日快乐啊 蠢猪
- [Panting]
- [dialing on car phone]
[line ringing]
come on, come on, come on!
‎拜托 快接啊 你个混蛋共产党员！
Pick up, pick up, pick
up, you commie bastards!
[ominous synth music playing]
[freezer humming]
[pull-tab clicks loudly]
- [whispers] quiet.
- [Whispers] oh, sorry.
‎-保持安静
‎-哦 抱歉
- How do you even drink that?
- Because it's delicious.
‎-你怎么还能喝得下？
‎-因为好喝
[mike and max] what?
‎什么？
It's like carpenter's the thing.
‎就像约翰卡朋特的《怪形》
The original is a classic,
‎原本是经典 毫无疑问
no question about it.
But the remake...
‎但是翻拍的...
[slurping loudly]
[satisfied sigh]
[smacking lips]
sweeter, bolder...
‎更甜 更大胆
Better.
‎更好
You're insane.
‎你是个疯子
So, you prefer the original thing?
‎所以你更喜欢看原版的《怪形》？
What? No, I'm not talking
about the thing,
‎什么？不 我不是在说《怪形》
‎我是在说新版的可乐
i'm talking about new coke.
It's the same concept, dude.
‎概念一样 朋友
Uh, actually, it's not the same concept.
‎事实上 概念并不一样
It is the same concept.
‎是同一个概念
- No, it's not.
- [Yells] yes, it is.
‎-不 不是的
‎-就是
hey.
‎喂
Sorry.
‎-抱歉
Did you... Find him?
‎你...找到他了吗？
[lucas] the movies?
‎电影院？
Dustin's so freaked out about the gate,
‎达斯汀被门吓坏了 决定去看电影？
he decides to go watch a movie?
Yeah, makes total sense.
‎是啊 完全说得通
You're positive he said
"gate" and not "great"?
‎你确定他说的是"门" 不是"美"吗？
Yeah, like, "this movie
i'm watching is great."
‎是 比如"我看的这电影可美了"
Sounded like "gate".
‎听起来像是"门"
Which would explain how the
mind flayer's still alive.
‎这也就解释了夺心魔为什么还活着
- Yeah, we just have to shut it again.
- Then the monster dies.
‎-是啊 我们必须要再次把门关上
‎-然后怪物就会死
But if not, we always
have lucas' fireworks.
‎如果不成功
‎反正还有卢卡斯的烟花可以用
Keep mocking my plan,
max. Keep mocking it.
‎继续嘲笑我的计划吧 麦克斯
‎继续嘲笑
I wanna hear you say it again,
because you keep doubting me.
‎我想听你再说一遍
‎因为你一直在怀疑我
You keep doubting me!
- [Max] ridiculous.
- [Lucas] will?
‎-荒唐的计划
‎-那我可得证明你是错的了 对不对？
We're gonna prove 'em wrong, right?
[eerie synth music playing]
[screeching]
[steve groans]
the ceiling stopped spinning for me.
‎我看屋顶的时候已经不再转了
Is it still spinning for you?
‎你呢？
Holy shit.
‎老天
no.
‎不转了
You think we puked it all up?
‎你觉得我们是都吐出来了吗？
Maybe. Ask me something.
‎也许吧 问我一些问题
[in russian accent] interrogate me.
‎质问我
Okay. Interrogate you. Sure.
‎好的 质问你 当然
Um...
When was the last time
you, uh, peed your pants?
‎你上一次吓到尿湿裤子是什么时候？
Today.
‎今天
What?
‎什么？
When the russian doctor
took out the bone saw.
‎俄国医生拿出骨锯的时候
[laughs] oh, my god.
‎哦 老天
It was just a little bit, though.
‎但只尿了一点点
Yeah, it's definitely
still in her system.
‎是 我们体内肯定还有药
[laughs]
[groans]
[robin] oh...
- All right, my turn.
- Okay.
‎-好了 轮到我了
‎-好的
Hit me.
‎问吧
Have you...
‎你有没有...
Ever been in love?
‎爱过谁？
Yep. Nancy wheeler.
‎有 南茜惠勒 高四第一学期
First semester, senior year.
[imitates gunshot, chuckles]
oh, my god.
‎我的天
She's such a priss.
‎她太娇气了
[steve] hm.
Turns out, not really.
‎结果并不是
[scoffs] are you still
in love with nancy?
‎你还爱着南茜吗？
- No.
- Why not?
‎-不了
‎-为什么？
I think it's because I found someone
who's a little bit better for me.
‎我觉得是因为
‎我找到了一个更适合我的人
[chuckles] it's crazy.
‎很疯狂
Ever since dustin got
home, he's been saying,
‎达斯汀回家之后 就一直在说
"you know, you gotta find your
suzie. You gotta find your suzie."
‎"你必须找到你的苏西"
Wait, who's suzie?
‎慢着 苏西是谁？
It's some girl from camp,
I guess his girlfriend.
‎夏令营个的一个姑娘
‎我猜是他的女朋友吧
To be honest with you, I'm
not 100% sure she's even real.
‎老实说 我并不能百分之百确定
‎她是真实存在的
But that's not... That's
not really the point.
‎但重点不在这里
That doesn't matter.
The point is, this girl,
‎这不重要 重点是这个女孩
‎我喜欢的这个
you know, the one that I like,
it's somebody that I...
Didn't even talk to in school.
‎是我上学时都没有说过话的
And I don't even know why.
‎我都不知道为什么
Maybe 'cause tommy h.
Would've made fun of me or...
‎也许是因为汤米H会嘲笑我 或者...
I wouldn't be...
‎我会成不了舞会国王
Prom king.
It's stupid. I mean, dustin's right,
‎很蠢 达斯汀说得对
‎反正就是一堆胡扯的玩意儿
it's all just a bunch
of bullshit anyways.
Because, when I think about it,
‎因为 仔细想想
I should've been hanging out
with this girl the whole time.
‎我应该一直和这个女孩一起玩才对
First of all, she's
hilarious. She's so funny.
‎首先 她超级搞笑 非常风趣
I feel like, this summer,
I have laughed harder
‎我觉得今年夏天 我笑得特别厉害
than I have laughed...
‎很久没有笑得这么厉害了
In a really long time.
And she's smart.
‎她还很聪明
Way smarter than me.
‎比我聪明多了
You know, she can crack, like,
top secret russian codes and...
‎你知道 她能解开绝密俄国代码
You know? She's honestly unlike
anyone I've ever even met before.
‎她完全不像任何我之前认识的人
Robin?
‎罗宾？
[tapping on stall]
robin, did you just od in there?
‎罗宾 你是吸毒过量了吗？
No. [sighs]
‎没有
i...
‎我还活着
am still alive.
[deep sigh]
[robin] the floor's disgusting.
‎地板可脏了
Yeah, well, I already
got a bunch of blood
‎反正我衣服上
‎也已经有好多血和呕吐物了 所以...
and puke on my shirt, so...
What do you think?
‎你怎么想？
About?
‎关于什么？
This girl.
‎这个女孩
She sounds awesome.
‎她听起来很棒
She is awesome. And what about the guy?
‎她的确很棒 那这个男的呢？
I think he's on drugs, and
he's not thinking straight.
‎我觉得他嗑了药 脑子不清楚
Really? 'cause I think he's thinking
a lot more clearly than usual.
‎真的吗？
‎因为我觉得他比平时想得更清楚
He's not.
‎不是的
Look...
‎听着
He doesn't even know this girl.
‎他都不了解这个女孩
And if he did know her,
‎如果他了解了她 真正了解了她
like... Like really know her,
I don't think he'd even
want to be her friend.
‎我觉得他会连她的朋友都不想当
No, that's not true.
No way is that true.
‎不 不是这样的 不可能的
Listen to me, steve.
‎听我说 史蒂夫
It's shocked me to my core,
‎我真的彻底地被震惊到了
but I like you.
‎但我喜欢你
I really like you.
‎我真的喜欢你
But I'm not like your other friends.
‎但我和你其他的朋友不一样
And I'm not like nancy wheeler.
‎我也不像南茜惠勒
Robin, that's exactly why I like you.
‎罗宾 这正是我喜欢你的原因
[robin scoffs]
do you remember what I
said about click's class?
‎你还记得我说的
‎克里克老师的课的事吗？
About me being jealous
and, like, obsessed?
‎说我嫉妒、痴迷的那件事？
Yeah.
‎记得
It isn't because I had a crush on you.
‎那并不是因为我暗恋你
It's because...
‎而是因为...
She wouldn't stop staring at you.
‎她一直盯着你看
Mrs. Click?
‎克里克老师？
[chuckles]
tammy thompson.
‎塔米汤普森
I wanted her to look at me.
‎我想要她看我
But... She couldn't pull
her eyes away from you
‎但她完全不能把眼睛从你
and your stupid hair.
‎和你愚蠢的头发上移开
And I didn't understand,
because you would get
‎我不理解
‎因为你会把贝果面包的面包屑
bagel crumbs all over the floor.
‎搞得地上到处都是
And you asked dumb questions.
‎你还会问愚蠢的问题
‎而且你那时候还是个浑球
And you were a douchebag.
And... And you didn't
even like her and...
‎你甚至都不喜欢她 而且...
I would go home...
‎我会回家对着我的枕头大吼
And just scream into my pillow.
But tammy thompson's a girl.
‎但塔米汤普森是个女孩
[softly] steve.
‎史蒂夫
Yeah?
‎怎么了？
oh.
Holy shit.
‎-老天
‎-是的
Yeah.
Holy shit.
‎老天
Steve...
‎史蒂夫
Did you od over there?
‎你是吸毒过量了吗？
No, I just, uh...
‎没有 只是...
Just thinking.
‎在思考
Okay.
‎好的
I mean, yeah.
‎我想说 是的
Tammy thompson, you know,
she's cute and all, but...
‎塔米汤普森挺漂亮的 但是...
I mean,
‎她是个蠢蛋
she's a total dud.
She is not.
‎她才不是
Yes, she is. She wants
to be, like, a singer.
‎她就是 她还想做歌手
She wants to move to,
like, nashville and shit.
‎她还想搬去纳什维尔之类的地方去
- She has dreams.
- She can't even hold a tune.
‎-她有梦想
‎-她唱歌跑调
She's practically tone-deaf.
Have you heard her?
‎基本上就是五音不全
‎你听过她唱歌吗？
- [Robin chuckles]
- all the time.
‎一直都是
[singing atonally] ♪
you see me now tonight ♪
- shut up.
- ♪ you see me... ♪
‎闭嘴
- she does not sound like that.
- She sounds exactly...
‎-她唱歌才不是那样的
‎-一模一样...
- That's a great impersonation of her.
- She does not.
‎-学得超级像
‎-她才不是那样唱歌的
You sound like a muppet.
‎你听起来像是个布偶
She sounds like a muppet.
‎她听起来就像是个布偶
She sounds like a muppet giving birth.
‎她听起来像是个在分娩中的布偶
[both laughing]
[sings like kermit] ♪ and
if you could hold me tight ♪
[both sing atonally] ♪
we'll be holding on forever ♪
- exactly.
- [Laughs] I know!
‎-就是这样
‎-我知道
Okay.
‎好了 什么鬼？
What the hell?
[both laugh]
[intense synth music playing]
[creature shrieks weakly]
[monstrous screeching]
[cheering and laughing]
[alexei, in russian] and why all this?
‎为什么搞这么些东西？
If I just turn the keys,
it's like turning off a car.
‎如果我只是拧钥匙 就像关掉车引擎
But then the car still
works, does it not?
‎但车还能用 不是吗？
[in russian] yes.
‎是的
And do you want the car to still
work or do you want it to explode?
‎你想要车还能用还是希望车炸掉？
I want the car to explode.
‎我想要车炸掉
Good. Then do this.
‎好的 那就这么做
Just make sure you are
nowhere near it when it does.
‎但是你得确保这么做的时候
‎离它远远的 结果可不好看
It is not pretty.
Turns people into dust.
‎会把人炸成灰
And then...
‎然后...
It's over.
‎就结束了
[chuckles]
and I become an american
citizen and join in the fun, yes?
‎然后我就能成为美国公民
‎加入你们一起玩了 是不是？
Who said you had to be an
american to join the fun?
‎谁说你非得成为美国公民
‎才能和我们一起玩的？
[carnival music playing]
[crowd cheering]
[in russian] it doesn't get more
american than this, my friend.
‎你绝对找不到比这更美国的经历了
‎我的朋友
Fatty foods, ugly decadence,
‎油腻的食物、丑陋的颓废
rigged games...
‎被操纵的游戏
[in english] fifteen tickets, please.
‎要15张票 谢谢
[cheering]
- they are rigged, these games?
- [In russian] yes.
‎-这些游戏是被操纵的？
‎-是
[balloon pops]
they do not look rigged.
‎看起来不像是啊
That's just it, my dear alexei.
‎这就对了 我亲爱的阿列克谢
They have been designed to
present the illusion of fairness!
‎它们设计出来
‎就是为了做出公平的假象
But it's all a scam, a trick,
‎但其实都是骗局 都是戏法
to put your money in
the rich man's pocket.
‎把你的钱骗入有钱人的口袋里
That, my dear friend, is...
‎我亲爱的朋友 这就是...
America.
‎美国
But, hey...
‎但是呢
Knock yourself out.
‎请别客气
[carnival barker yelling]
where are you going?
‎你要去哪儿？
To get us the closest
thing to food I can find.
‎去给我们找一些接近食物的东西吃
Hey. Hey.
‎嘿
[joyce] karen.
‎凯伦
[carnival barker] step right up!
[karen] ... Feel the wind push
you back and it's gonna...
- [Ted] hold on. Do we have seat belts?
- Hey, karen.
‎-嘿 凯伦
‎-乔伊斯！
Joyce!
Oh, my gosh! How funny to see you here!
‎-老天 在这儿见到你可真巧了
‎-孩子们呢？
Where are the kids?
I... I haven't seen them. I
don't think they're here yet.
‎我还没见到他们 我觉得他们还没到
- You three, up against the wall!
- No, where are they?
‎你们三个人 靠墙站
Oh, my gosh, I can hardly
keep track these days.
‎他们在哪儿？
‎老天 这段时间我几乎都跟不上他们
Uh, they were at, uh...
‎他们先是在达斯汀家
‎然后在卢卡斯家
Dustin's, then lucas's,
- then max's.
- Max...
‎-然后麦克斯家
‎-麦克斯
- You know how it is. Summer!
- [Alarm blaring]
‎你们懂的 夏天！
probably getting into
some kinda trouble.
‎八成在哪儿惹事呢
[ride door whirring]
last warning, you two.
Up against the wall!
‎最后一次警告 你们俩靠墙站好
Hold the ride!
‎先别开
On your life, magnum.
‎想得美 夏威夷神探
[all exclaiming]
‎开始了
[ted murmurs]
woo! Here we go!
‎开始啦！
Holy smokes!
‎我的老天爷！
[ted] holy smokes!
[rapid carnival music playing]
[doc] roads?
‎路？我们要去的地方不需要路
Where we're going, we don't need roads.
[cheering]
[indistinct chatter]
[door hinge creaking]
[dustin] and...
‎准备...
Blend.
‎混入人群
[woman] it is so good!
‎太优秀了！
- Well, shit, that worked.
- Course it worked.
‎-妈的 居然成功了
‎-当然成功了
We just have to get on the bus
with the rest of these plebes,
‎我们只需要
‎和这些老百姓们一起坐上公交车
and home sweet home, here we come.
‎然后就可以回家啦
- Uh, dustin?
- What?
‎-达斯汀？
‎-怎么了？
Yeah, we might not
wanna go to your house.
‎我们可能不想去你家
why?
‎为什么？
Well, I might've told
them your full name.
‎我可能把你的全名告诉了他们
- What is wrong with you?
- Dude, I was drugged.
‎-你什么毛病？
‎-朋友 我被下了药啊
- So?
‎-所以呢？
So, you resist. You tough it
out. You tough it out like a man.
‎你坚持住 你熬过去 像个男子汉一样
Oh, yeah, it's easy for you to say.
‎是啊 你站着说话不腰疼
Guys?
‎各位？
Sorry for the inconvenience.
Have a pleasant evening.
‎抱歉给你添麻烦了 祝你今晚愉快
Abort.
‎终止计划
[suspenseful music playing]
abort. Abort.
‎终止计划
[panting]
[steve] shit.
‎妈的
[robin] okay.
‎好的
[steve] come on, let's go, let's go.
‎快 快走
[onlookers cheering]
that's three green!
‎三个绿色气球
And here's dart number four!
‎给你第4枚飞镖
[carnival music playing]
[cheering]
one more for the big prize!
‎再来一个就能拿大奖
You can do it, mister!
‎你能做到的 先生
- [Bell ringing]
- [loud cheering]
[man] we have a winner!
‎赢家产生了！
[barker] step right up,
ladies and gentlemen!
‎女士们先生们 请上前来
‎把你们的票拿到这里来！
Get your tickets right here!
Murray!
‎穆雷！
[in russian] look!
‎你看！
It's not rigged!
‎没有被操纵
ah!
[laughs like woody woodpecker]
it's not rigged.
‎没有被操纵
[murray laughs heartily]
[ominous music playing]
[carnival audio fades]
[silenced gunshot]
[in russian] traitor.
‎叛徒
[faintly] alexei!
‎阿列克谢！
[feedback whining]
[clown's laughter
echoing in slow motion]
[resuming normal volume] alexei!
‎阿列克谢！
[carnival audio resumes]
[in english] oh, no.
Oh, my god. Let's go.
‎哦 不 老天 我们走
[alexei grunts and coughs]
- easy.
- [Alexei groans]
‎小心点
[in russian] keep pressure on it.
‎用力压住
I'll get you help.
‎我去找人帮忙
I'll get help.
[suspenseful synth music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[crowd cheering]
jim... Jim.
‎吉姆！吉姆！
jim!
They got alexei, jim!
‎他们找到阿列克谢了 吉姆！
Jim! Alexei! They got alexei, jim!
‎吉姆 阿列克谢！
‎他们找到了阿列克谢 吉姆！
[exhales sharply]
we gotta go.
‎我们得跑了
- We gotta go.
- What?
‎什么？
[hopper] let's go.
‎快走
They make an odd couple, don't they?
‎他们俩还真是古怪的一对 是不是？
Well, it's like they say,
‎老话说得好
there's someone for everyone.
‎每个人都有适合的另一半
[carnival music playing]
[bell ringing]
[karen sighs deeply]
[suspenseful music playing]
[crowd exclaims]
[male vendor] who wants a hot dog?
‎谁想吃热狗？
Find murray, get the car,
‎找到穆雷 去开车
- bring it around back.
- Okay.
‎-把车给开过来
‎-好的
[recording of cackling laughter]
[in russian] heading to "big top".
‎正在前往"大尖顶" 在游乐场东北方
Northeast side of the fair.
[carnival barker] step right
up, ladies and gentlemen!
‎快上来吧 女士们先生们
Get your tickets to the big top here!
‎把你的票拿到大尖顶这里玩吧
[barker speaking indistinctly]
...this side of the mississippi.
Hey! Get your kids outta here! Police!
‎嘿！把你们的孩子们带出去 警察！
Get 'em out of here! Go!
‎快把他们带出去 快走！
[barker] you, sir!
Step on up!
I see you eyeing the maze!
Don't be surprised! Don't be scared!
[crowd cheering]
[barker] step on up, sir!
[recording of cackling laughter]
[eerie male voice] do you
dare enter the cave of horrors?
‎你有胆量进入恐怖洞穴吗？
You never know what you
might find around the corner.
‎你永远都不会知道在转角会发现什么
[recording of eerie giggling]
don't show your fear in
the presence of the tiger.
‎看到老虎可千万别害怕
[tiger's roar sounds]
or you may never escape this cave alive.
‎否则你就没法活着走出这个洞穴
- [Tiger's roar sounds]
- [hopper yells]
[fighting grunts]
[gasps]
[screams]
[panting]
alexei!
‎阿列克谢
Oh, my god.
‎老天
I... I just left for a minute...
‎我就离开了他一分钟 去买玉米热狗
For a corn dog.
- [Joyce cries]
- a stupid corn dog.
‎愚蠢的玉米热狗
Oh, god.
‎哦 老天
Oh, no.
‎哦 不
- [Man grunts]
- [carnival music playing]
[fighting grunts]
[man groans]
[hopper yells]
[hopper grunts]
[man wails in pain]
[man groans]
[hopper yells]
[intense synth music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[panting]
[indistinct male voice on radio]
[man on radio, in russian] vasilev,
are you there? Vasilev? Answer!
‎瓦西列夫 你在吗？
‎瓦西列夫 回答我！
[male voice continues in russian]
[tiger's roar sounds]
[recording of cackling laughter]
[carnival music playing]
what are you doing?
‎你干什么？
hey!
‎喂！
- Larry.
- Joyce.
‎-拉里
‎-乔伊斯
[joyce grunts]
[larry wails in pain]
ooh! [groans]
[man] yeah, lady!
‎好样的 女士！
[suspenseful synth music playing]
[silenced gunshots]
[hopper] hey.
‎嘿！
[silenced gunshots]
[men speaking russian]
[gasps]
[recording of cackling laughter]
[gasps for air, groans]
[grigori coughs]
[man, in russian] comrade!
‎同志
Get off me!
‎别碰我
[recording of cackling laughter]
[sighs]
goddamn!
‎该死的狗娘养的！
Son of a bitch!
[grunting]
[groans]
[grunts]
hey!
‎嘿！
[hopper] hit it. Hit it! Go! Go!
‎快开！走！
Alexei?
‎阿列克谢呢？
[man on radio, in russian]
on the lower level...
‎...在下层
Hey, translate.
‎嘿 翻译
We've found the children.
‎再说一次 我们找到了孩子们
They are still in the mall. Lower level.
‎他们还在商场里 在下层
[in russian] keep all
entrances locked down.
‎所有入口保持封锁状态
I repeat...
‎再说一次 所有入口保持封锁状态
Keep all entrances locked down.
[squeaking sound]
[quietly] everyone, get over here.
‎所有人都过来
I found them.
‎我找到他们了
[kids panting]
[panting]
- [car alarm wailing]
- [all gasping]
[horn honking]
[in russian] what the hell?
‎什么鬼？
[intense synth music playing]
[men groaning]
[steam hissing]
[metal clattering]
[dramatic synth music playing]
[laughing] you flung that
thing like a hot wheel!
‎你丢那玩意儿像丢风火轮一样
[dustin grunts]
- lucas?
- What are you doing here?
‎-卢卡斯？
‎-你在这里干什么？
Ask them. It's their fault.
‎问他们 是他们的错
True, yeah. Totally true.
It's absolutely our fault.
‎没错 完全正确 绝对是我们的错
I don't understand what
happened to that car.
‎我不明白那车是怎么回事
El has superpowers.
‎艾尔有超能力
- [Robin] I'm sorry?
- Superpowers. She threw it with her mind.
‎-对不起？
‎-超能力 她用脑子把车丢了出去
- C'mon, catch up.
- That's el?
‎-拜托你跟上
‎-她就是艾尔？
- Who's el?
- I'm sorry, who are you?
‎-谁是艾尔？
‎-抱歉 你是谁？
- I'm robin. I work with steve.
- She cracked the top secret code.
‎-我是罗宾 史蒂夫的同事
‎-她破解了绝密代码
Yeah, which is how we found
out about the russians.
‎我们是因为她才发现俄国人的事的
Russians? Wait, what russians?
‎俄国人？慢着 什么俄国人？
- The russians!
- Those were russians?
‎-俄国人
‎-那些是俄国人？
- Some of them.
- What are you talking about?
‎-有一些是
‎-你们在说什么？
- Didn't you hear our code red?
- Yeah.
‎-你听到我们的红色警报了？
‎-是
- Couldn't understand what you were saying.
- Goddamn low battery.
‎-但你说的话有一半都听不懂
‎-该死的低电量
How many times do I have to
tell you with the low battery?
‎我要和你说多少次 要节约用电？
Well, everything worked out, didn't it?
‎一切都解决了 不是吗？
- Worked out? We almost died.
- Yeah, but we didn't, did we?
‎解决？我们差点就死了
‎-是 但我们没死 对不对？
‎-是 但就差那么一点点
- [Steve] it was pretty damn close.
- [Lucas] okay, russians?
‎好的 他们是俄国人
‎就意味着他们在为俄国政府工作？
As in, they're working
for the russian government?
- [Eleven panting]
- [dustin] what are you not comprehending?
‎你到底哪里没搞明白？
Am I not speaking english?
‎我说的不是英文吗？
- We have a full-blown red dawn situation.
- [Droning sound]
‎完全是《赤色黎明》翻版
[max] so this has nothing
to do with the gate?
‎所以这和门没有任何关系？
[dustin] it has everything
to do with the gate...
‎全部都和门有关系
[droning sound intensifies]
[eleven grunts, groans]
whoa, whoa, whoa.
- El! El!
- [Whimpering]
‎艾尔！
- [erica] what's wrong with her?
- What's wrong?
‎-她怎么了？
‎-怎么了？
My leg. My leg.
‎我的腿
Her leg, her leg. Okay.
‎她的腿 好的
[eleven panting]
- get that off.
- Okay.
‎-拿下来
‎-好的
[all exclaim in disgust]
[erica groans]
[gasps]
[intense synth music playing]
[grunting]
[wailing]
el! El!
‎艾尔！
[wailing]
[mike] el! El, are you okay?
‎艾尔 你没事吧？
El! El!
‎艾尔！
el!
[screaming]
[intense synth music playing]
‎字幕制作：美国青少年英语 （微信公众号&喜马拉雅主播）
[monkey screeching]